Freeze! Drop him.
꼼짝마! 내려놔!
마스크 벗어
Take your masks off.
Do it!
어서!
풀어줘
Untie him.
가만 있어봐
Stay still, hold still,
hold still.
가만히 좀 있으라니까
호들갑 떨지마, 찰스
Man up, Charles.
왜 이런 짓을 하는 거야?
Why would you do this to me?
Sorry, man,
미안해, 캡틴 총각 파티 때
it was a practice run
for when we kidnap Awesome
for his bachelor party.
납치할 거 미리 연습한 거야
너넨 초대도 못 받았잖아!
You guys aren't even invited!
그래, 그니까 가고 싶으면
Right, right,
what finer way to be invited
than to kidnap
the guest of honor?
주빈을 납치하는 게 최고지 않겠어?
총각 파티는
술과 여자가 무료인 신성한 곳이야
A bachelor party
is a mythical place
where booze
무릉 도원이지
It's Xanadu.
엄마야!
Oh, my God!
그만해요! 그만!
Stop it!
그만해요!
You... stop it!
잘가, 난 자러 갈래
Okay, I'm going to bed.
What the heck?!
척?
Chuck?
Bartowski?
바토스키?
장군님! 안녕하세요
General! Hey.
여긴 어떻게..
What are you, what are you...
I wanted a private word
with you.
자네랑 조용히 할 얘기가 있네
방해해서 미안하네
Pardon the intrusion.
지금요?
On this moment?
아님 제 인생에서요?
Or on my life in general?
I'd like to know if your
relationship with Agent Walker
자네와 워커 요원과의 관계가
직무 수행에
방해가 되는 건 아닌지 알고 싶네
is compromising
your job performance.
네? 그게 무슨 말씀이세요?
How do you mean?
What does that mean?
상황이 곤란하진 않나?
Has your situation
gotten too complicated?
What? With, with Sarah?
네? 새라랑요?
아뇨, 전혀요
No, God, no.
아뇨 전 새라랑 일해서
좋은 걸요
No, Sarah Walker
is a pleasure to work with.
기쁘기까지 해요
A delight, even.
I want facts, I don't care
about your feelings.
사실대로 말하게
난 자네 감정엔 관심 없어
- 감정이라뇨?
- 이거 말이네
What feelings?
These feelings:
- 새라 나랑 데이트 안할래요?
- 진짜 데이트요?
Sarah, you want to go
on a date with me?
A real date?
새라를 만난 게
내 인생에서 최고의 사건이에요
Sarah, you're the greatest thing
that's ever happened to me.
내 감정을 정리할
시간이 필요해요
I guess I wouldn't mind time
to sort out my feelings.
우리 엄마의 팔찌에요
My mother's charm bracelet.
아빠가 주셨대요
My dad gave it to her.
I'm crazy about you
and always have been.
난 새라를 좋아해요
항상 그랬어요
My job is to make sure
you're protected
자네가 내 팀원과
감정적으로 얽히지 않고
자넬 안전하게 보호하는 것이
내 일이네
without interloping emotional
complications from my team.
49-B를 해야겠어
We're going to have
to do a 49-B.
네, 49-B가 뭔지 말씀을 해주시면
도움이 될 것..
Okay, if you could just tell me
what a 49-B is
that would help...
?????
척스터
Chuckster.
몸 청소 할 시간이야
Time to flush out
your system, dude.
세상에
Oh. Oh, God.
No, I'm good
with my clog.
싫어요, 전 꽉 막혀도 괜찮아요
총각 파티 말인데요
Hey, about your
bachelor party,
do you still want to do
that camping thing
정말 다른 사람들처럼 안하고
or, uh, do you want to do
something more traditional,
캠핑 가는 거 괜찮겠어요?
뭐해?
or...?
Hey.
척, 이게 반송됐어
Chuck, uh, this came back
in the mail for you.
아빠한테 보낸 편지
It's from Dad.
정말 유감이야 누나
I'm so sorry, Ellie.
계속 찾아볼게
I'll keep searching.
내 걱정은 하지마
You know what?
Don't worry about it.
기대가 없으면
실망도 없는 법이잖아, 그치?
You can't get disappointed
if you don't
have expectations, right?
참, 들어오면서
총각 파티 얘기 들었어
So, um, I was overhearing
about the bachelor party.
For the record, I don't care
what you guys do,
둘이서 뭘 하든 난 상관 없어
왜냐면 전적으로 자길 믿으니까
because I trust you
completely.
Which is why
I'm marrying you.
그래서 내가 자기랑
결혼하는 거야
What is that?
이게 뭐야?
That is the taste
of a healthy colon.
건강한 대장을 위한 맛이지
Who's General Beckman?
What?
벡맨 장군이 누구야? / 네?
비디오 게임이에요
게임에서 쓰는 이름이요
Video game stuff.
Yeah, it's video game stuff.
It's top-secret vide game stuff
that I-I, you know,
일급 비밀 비디오 게임 같은 거예요
말 안하기로 해서
말 못해요
I'd be breaking all kinds
of rules to talk about it.
모건? / 네
Morgan, huh?
Yeah.
So if Morgan's
General Beckman, who are you?
모건은 벡맨 장군이고
넌 뭐야?
그게...
Uh, well...
I am Special Agent Carmichael.
카마이클 특수요원이요
카마이클이라, 맘에 드네
Carmichael. I like it.
새라
Sarah. Hey, Sarah,
I messed up.
General Beckman,
저 실수한 것 같아요
벡멘 장군님이 저한테
she called me, asked me
about our relationship.
우리가 무슨 사이냐고 물으셨어요
그 때 그 얘기 기억나죠
And, you know that conversation,
the one where I
might've maybe
mentioned
제가 당신이 너무 좋다고 했던 거요
Well, I tried to cover it,
제가 아니라고 했는데
믿으시는 것 같지가 않아요
but I'm not so sure
that she bought it.
Wha-- where's Sarah?
새라는 어딨어요?
I'm Agent Alex Forrest.
알렉스 포레스트 요원이라고 해
벡맨 장군님이 보내셨지
General Beckman sent me.
내가 네 49-B 야
I'm your 49-B.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
영어자막 : http://www.ragbear.com
싱크수정 / 한글자막
김호정(hojeong_@nate.com)
Chuck 2x18
Chuck Versus the Broken Heart
For the chuck team
I'm sure you've all had a chance
to welcome Agent Alex Forrest.
다들 알렉스 포레스트 요원과
인사 나눴겠지
물론입니다, 장군님
Of course, General.
그럼 바로 시작하지
Then onto the matter at hand.
수 년째 아프가니스탄
동굴에서 숨어 지내서
We're all familiar
with the elusive leader
of a terrorist group
who has been hiding in the
Afghani caves for years:
우리가 계속 놓치고 있는
테러리스트 리더 하산 카리드에 대해
Hassan Khalid.
다들 잘 알고 있겠지
I dream of finding him.
- 꼭 잡고야 말겠어
A member of Khalid's
inner circle is this man:
이 사람은 칼리드의 측근인
Rashad Ahmad.
라시드 아마드네
아마드는 칼리드이 저지른
모든 불법에 연루된 자야
Ahmad is privy
to all of Khalid's
nefarious plans.
칼리드 대신 LA에서
은행 업무를 보다가
While on banking business
for Khalid in Los Angeles,
아마드로 의심되는 자가
심장 발작을 일으켰네
a man we believe to be Ahmad
had a heart attack.
맥박 조정기가 필요해서
해리 라임이라는
He needs a pacemaker and
has checked into a hospital
under the pseudonym: Harry Lime.
가명으로 병원에 입원했네
그 남자가 아마드라고 생각하십니까?
You believe this
man to be Ahmad?
그게 자네들 임무야
That is the mission.
Intelligence has only
been able to obtain
grainy satellite
현재로선 입수된 정보가
아마드의 희미한
위성 사진뿐이 없네
바토스키 자네는
자네만의 기술을 이용해서
Mr. Bartowski, using his unique
skill set, must infiltrate
the hospital
병원에 잠입하여
아마드의 신원을 확인하게
- 질문 있나?
- 간단하겠네요, 장군님
Questions?
Sounds straightforward,
General.
네, 저 질문 있어요
Yeah, I have a question.
Just a teeny little one.
아주 작은 질문이
하나 있어요
What exactly is a 49-B?
정확하게 49-B가 뭐죠?
Mind fielding that one,
Agent Walker?
대신 알려주겠나, 워커 요원?
포레스트 요원은
제 업무를 평가하기 위해 왔고
Agent Forrest is here
to assess my performance.
And during
my evaluation period,
평가 기간 동안에는
척의 담당자 역할을 수행합니다
she will assume
the role
of the asset's handler.
Thank you.
고맙네
That will be all.
이상이네
어떻게 된 일이에요?
What?
What is this all about?
미안해요, 더 이상의 얘기는
절차상 할 수가 없어요
I'm sorry,
to discuss this further
would be a breach of protocol.
"To discuss this further
would be a breach of protocol"?
"더 이상의 얘기는
절차상 할 수가 없어요"?
Is it possible that
someone kidnapped Sarah
이러다가 누가
새라를 납치해서
영혼도 없는 복제품이랑
바꿔놓는 거 아니에요?
and replaced her
with some kind of
soulless replica?
맞춰볼까
Let me guess. You want to talk about
your feelings, Bartowski?
네 기분이 어떤지
말하고 싶다는 거지?
네 / 안돼
Please.
Wrong!
애초부터 그것때문에
49-B 가 나타난 거야
That's what got
the 49-B involved
in the first place.
How could...
Chuck.
척
친구, 캡틴 총각 파티때문에
부탁하러 왔어
All right, buddy, we are here
to plead our case
about Awesome's
You know what?Not now, guys, I'm right
in the middle of something.
나중에 하자
지금은 바빠
The world revolves
around the sun,
지구는 태양을 중심으로 돌지
널 중심으로 도는 게 아냐
Charles, not you.
천문학으로 한방 먹였는데
Ooh, astronomy snap.
자 이제 그만해
Okay. It's just that--
다시 한 번 더 생각해줘
we just-- we'd like you
to reconsider.
Reconsider what?
You guys aren't even invited!
뭘 더 생각해?
너넨 초대도 안 받았다니까?
네가 얘기해
아님 내가 한다
You tell him or I will.
제프랑 나...
Jeff and I...
한번도 총각파티 못 가봤어
we've never been
to a bachelor party.
여자가 결혼해 줄만큼
Never known anyone
qualified enough to land
a woman for life.
제정신인 사람을 사겨본 적이 없어
So, please,
please.
Please, please.
그니까 제발, 제발 부탁이야
부탁할게 / 아니 안돼
Please...
No and no.
알았어, 그럼 이건 어때
Okay,
how about this? As a plus,
빅 마이크가 엄마랑
데이트를 하면서
since Big Mike
has been dating my mother,
나한테 열쇠를 맡겼어
he's made me lock up.
그니까 여길
파티 장소로 쓰면
So, we can use this place
for the party,
돈을 아낄 수가 있겠지?
save a little cash
and guess what?
그 돈을 댄서들한테 쓰는 거야
Spend it on lady dancers.
Pow!
댄서를 부르자
Lady dancers.
Pow.
Hey now. Hey now.
We're talking
serious...
The answer's no.
- 댄서를 불러서..
- 내 대답은 '노'야
Hey...
Oh, please.
척, 제발
Don't-don't say no.
거절하지 말고
생각해 보겠다고 해줘
Say you'll wrap
your mind around it.
Hey, does the new girl know
about, uh...
새라, 새로 온 여자도
혹시 알아요?
아뇨
No.
She won't know
that top secret information
지금 상황이 계속 되지 않는 한
unless her position
becomes permanent.
그런 일급 비밀은
알려주지 않아요
계속되다니 무슨 뜻이에요?
What, what do you
mean permanent?
It's not going to happen.
그럴 일 없을 거예요
The 49-B will come in,
make her findings
and be on her way.
49-B는 와서 할일 마치면
다시 돌아갈테니까요
저기 새라, 미안해요
Hey, uh,
I'm sorry, Sarah.
뭐가요?
For what?
I didn't mean to get you in
trouble at work 'cause I told
you my feelings.
내 감정을 얘기한 게
새라를 곤란하게 만들줄은 몰랐어요
녹화되고 있는 줄도 몰랐고요
I didn't know
I was being taped
that much.
아뇨 괜찮아요, 정말요
No, it's fine.
Really.
I've just been kind of
stressed out lately.
요즘 들어 스트레스를
많이 받아서 그래요
You know,
I promised Ellie that I'd find our dad
to walk her down the aisle,
내가 누나한테 결혼식 때
아빠랑 손잡고
걸어가게 해주겠다고
약속했었잖아요
노력 중인데
못 찾고 있거든요
but I've tried everything;
he's nowhere.
대체 어디 계신 건지
행방이 묘연해요
It's like he's fallen off
the face of the earth.
새라 보안 등급으로
Hey, you've
got clearance.
요새에 있는 컴퓨터에
아빠 이름 검색해 줄래요?
You mind running my dad's name
through the big Castle computer?
That's impossible.
그건 안돼요
당연히 안돼지
Damn right.
그런 짓을 했다간
해고 당하고
If Agent Walker
did that, not only
would she be fired
but potentially
face charges
of misappropriation
정부 정보 악용으로
기소될 테니까
개인 시간 끝났어요
Enough personal time.
이만 일하러 가요
We have work to do.
척과 난 병원에 들어가서
The asset and I
will enter the facility,
obtain uniforms
to assimilate and
attempt to confirm
유니폼을 구해서
직원으로 위장하고
아마드의 신원을 확인할게
내가 좀 도와줄까, 케이시?
Is there anything
I can do, Casey?
내가 알아서 할게
I got it.
케이시, 그건 뭐에요?
Casey, uh, what is that?
네가 해리 라임이
아마드인지 확인하면
You confirm Harry Lime is Ahmad,
내가 장비와
기증된 장기를 보관하는
I'll sneak into the hospital's
high-security area
병원 보안 구역에 들어갈 거야
where the equipment
and donor organs are kept.
Why? Aren't we just
gonna arrest him?
왜요? 체포 안할거예요?
미국 정부의 전술을 무시하지 마
Don't underestimate
the gamesmanship
of the U.S.
맥박 조정기를 이식하기 전에
Yeah, I'll place this
GLG-4000 inside
Ahmad's pacemaker
여기 이 GLG-4000를 심어둘 거야
후에 아마드가 하산 칼리드의
은신처로 돌아가면
When he returns
to Hassan Khalid's secret cave,
말 그대로 고성능 인간 도청기
역할을 하는 거야
he'll be a high-tech human bug.
그럼 우린 테러리스트들의
은신처도 알게 되고
Then not only will we know
the terrorists' secret location,
그들의 계획에서
한 발 앞서 나가게 있는 거지
but we'll be one step ahead
of their plans.
- 체크 메이트
Checkmate.
문 열어
Get the door.
다들 미쳤어요?
Are you guys crazy?
I can't go in here.
This is the hospital
where Ellie and
난 못 들어가요
여긴 누나랑 캡틴이
일하는 병원이잖아요
It's okay.
We checked their schedules.
괜찮아요
근무 시간표 확인해 봤는데
Ellie's not working today.
Devon is
mid-surgery.
엘리는 오늘 쉬는 날이고
데븐은 수술 중이에요
이봐
Hey,you're here to observe.
여기서 모니터 해
Stay in the van, Walker.
That's an order.
밴에 남아 있어
이건 명령이야
And what were you little
kids doing in there?
두 젊은이가 안에서 뭘 했대?
A little hanky-panky?
바람이라도 폈나?
뭐에요? 왜요?
What? Why?
Why would you do that?
왜 그랬어요?
진정해, 진정제니까
Relax, I only tranqed her.
6시간~8시간 있으면 깰 거야
She'll be awake
six to eight hours.
다리나 잡아
Now grab a leg.
선생님
Oh, hey!
오늘 쉬시는 날인줄 알았는데요
I didn't think you were on
call today, Dr. Bartowski.
네, 근데 병원에서 자꾸
제 근무 시간을 바꿔버리네요
Yeah, well, they keep
switching my shifts around.
또 뵈요
See you.
You know, that grandma
was no threat to us.
그 할머니는 우리한테
아무 위협도 안되는데
I don't get why
you decided...
I don't decide.
- 어째서 그런 결정을..
- 내가 내린 결정 아냐
난 절차를 따를 뿐이야
Protocol dictates
my actions.
척
Chuck...
your sister is 30 feet
northeast of you.
엘리가 북동쪽 방향으로
1m 떨어진 곳에 있어요
선생님
Doctor...
네?
Yeah?
펜 가져가셔야죠
You forgot your pen.
빨리 숨어요
Now or never.
그자에요
It's him.
주치의 선생님 되십니까?
Are you his doctor?
물론이죠
Of course.
Am I not wearing
a doctor's coat?
의사 가운 입고 있는 거
안보이세요?
Who else would I be if not
one of this man's doctors?
의사가 아니면 누구겠어요?
박사님, 전 해리 라임씨의
개인 내과 의사입니다
Dr. Mohammed Zamir.
모하마드 자미르 박사입니다
Ah. Doctor.
박사님
Doctor.
- 박사님
And Doctor.
- 네, 박사님
Nurse, would you excuse us
for a moment, please?
간호사, 잠깐 자리 좀 비켜주겠어요?
I'd like to consult
the doctor privately, please.
박사님과 조용히
상의하고 싶은 게 있는데
Yes, yes, we will be
discussing doctor things
that only doctors
그래요, 의학 박사들만
이해할 수 있는
얘길 좀 해야겠으니까
이만 나가보세요
Please go.
제발 가지 마요
Please don't go.
Be right outside...
Doctor.
그럼 밖에 있겠습니다
박사님
Major, what's your 20?
소령, 지금 위치는?
In position.
도착했다
Identification affirmative.
신원이 확인됐다
Roger that.
Proceed.
알았다, 시작하겠다
Hey!
이봐요!
You!
Yeah?
아저씨! / 네?
806호 자궁 절제술 환자가
화장실에 못가겠대요
Hysterectomy in 806
didn't make it to the toilet.
You mind?
좀 도와줄래요?
You got it.
알겠습니다
Well, heart sounds
appear to be normal.
심장 소리는 정상같네요
For a patient with this type
of atypical
cardio-cardiac condition.
심장 상태가 좋지 않은
환자 치고는요
You should know
that this patient
is a very important man.
여기 이 분은
정말 중요하신 분입니다
Well, I... I took an oath
to treat my first
patient with the same
전 모든 환자를 공평하게
치료하겠다고 맹세한 사람입니다
kind of care
as every subsequent patient.
It's a very dangerous job
to be the surgeon
of a very important man.
아주 중요한 분을
수술하는 건
아주 위험한 일이지요
You understand
my meaning, Doctor?
제 말 이해하셨습니까, 박사님?
I'll do the best job
that I know how to do.
제가 아는 한에서
최선을 다하겠습니다
Your life depends on it.
이건 박사님 목숨이 달린 일입니다
If I have to eat
an apple a day
to keep that??? then bring on
the fresh fruit.
하루에 사과 하나면
의사가 필요없다는데
저런 의사라면
하나로는 안되겠는데요
Hey.
이봐
Security system
has been updated.
보안 시스템이 업데이트 됐나봐
I'll either need 40 minutes
to decrypt the code
or four ounces of C-4.
비밀번호를 알아내려면
40분은 걸려
아님 C4 100g은 있어야겠어
Or you could just
take out some doctor
and steal his card key.
아님 그냥 아무 의사나 골라서
열쇠를 훔쳐도 되지
네 방식 마음에 드는데
I like the cut of your jib.
Wow, you two are a match
made in a very frightening
part of Heaven.
둘이 어쩜 그렇게 똑같아요
Now, all we'll need
is some idiot doctor
이제 우리한테
제한 구역 열쇠를 줄
with a key card to get us
into the restricted area.
멍청한 의사 하나만 있으면 돼
안돼요
No way.
안돼요, 절대로 안돼요
No, no way,
absolutely not.
No, uh-uh, ???
I am not getting
my soon-to-be brother-in-law
싫어요, 곧 매형될 사람을
정부 스파이 임무에
참여하게 하고 싶지 않아요
절대 안돼요
involved in a government
spy mission-- no way.
다행이게도 너 같은 강력범이나
꼬마들에겐 투표권이 없어
Fortunately, you,
like felons and children,
don't get a vote.
우리가 접근할 수 있는
다른 의사는 없어?
Is there a different doctor
we can access?
그렇게 하면 이번 임무에서
척의 정체가 밝혀질 위험이 있어
This mission does put Chuck's
cover close to the action,
risking potential
exposure.
And boom-- the words
I was thinking
바로 그거에요
내 생각을
just came out of
Sarah's mouth.
딱 새라가 대신 해주네요
우리가 임무 얘긴 잘 통한다니까요
Connected professionally.
시간이 없어
No time, Bartowski.
카드키를 가진 의사는
둘 뿐이야
Only a couple docs
have that card key.
네 누나 남자친구가
그 중 하나고
Your sister's Ken doll
is one of them.
Well, how are you going
to do that? You can't just walk up
to Awesome and ask for it.
어떻게 할 생각인데요?
다짜고짜 가서
열쇠를 달라고 할 순 없잖아요
내 식대로 해결하지
I'll handle things my way.
No, wait, wait, wait!
안돼요! 잠시만요!
There will be no
tranqing... no tranqing.
절대로, 절대로
진정제를 써선 안돼요
모두를 만족시킬 방법을
알 것 같아요
I think I might know
how we can have our spy cake
and eat it, too.
What the...
뭐 하는 거야!
What are you doing?
짜잔!
Surprise!
너네 진짜 짱이다
You guys are awesome.
To the bachelor!
총각 파티 시작이다!
뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?
Visual souvenirs, dude.
기념으로 간직하려고
He does quite a bit
of scrapbooking.
쟤 이런 거 모으는 스크랩북 있잖아
말도 안돼
You got to be kidding me.
Listen to me, guys.
너희 내 말 잘 들어
What happens in the Buy More...
바이모어에서 생긴 일은
바이모어에 남는 거야
stays in the Buy More.
아 맞다
Oh, right.
그래, 알았어
Yes, no, I-I got it.
미안해
I'm... I'm sorry.
총각 파티는 처음이라
Bachelor
party virgin.
조심해
Lock it down. Okay, okay.
응, 알았어
Hey, hey, hey.
데븐
Uh... happy bachelor
party there, Captain.
총각 파티 축하해요, 캡틴
그래, 파티 열어줘서 고마워
벡맨 장군
Well, thanks
for all your help
throwing it,
Nothing gets by me.
난 못 속여
그래요
Okay.
제가 관찰해 본 결과
Based on my observations,
Agent Walker is far too
emotionally entwined
with the asset.
워커 요원은 바토스키와
매우 감정적으로 얽힌 사이입니다
워커 요원은 정해진
절차에 따라 결정을 내리지 않고
Her decisions
weren't made
with respect to
항상 명령보다 바토스키의
감정을 우선으로 생각합니다
She always places
the subject's feelings
above orders.
Is that your final assessment,
Agent Forrest?
그게 자네의 최종 평가인가?
그렇습니다
It is.
워커 요원
Agent Walker.
그동안 이번 임무를
수행하느라 수고 많았네
Thank you for your dedication
to this mission.
General, please, I...
장군님, 전..
하지만 지금 이 순간부터
But as of right now,
자네는 공식적으로
이번 임무에서 제외되네
your services
are officially terminated.
9시에 랭리로 돌아가게
Report back to Langley at 0900.
Please take good care of him.
나 대신 잘 돌봐줘
내 직무는 다할게
그 뜻이라면 말이야
I'll do my job,
if that's what you mean.
작별 인사만 하고
바로 떠날게
Well, I'll be on my way
as soon as I say
good-bye to him.
I don't think so.
그렇겐 안되지
이미 충분히 피해를
주지 않았나 싶은데
You've already done
enough damage here.
Chuck's my
mission now.
척은 이제 내 담당이야
No further contact.
더 이상 만나지 마
이건 명령이야
That's an order.
소중한 사랑을 위하여
To finding the love
of your life.
건배
Hey!
Happy bachelor party, my friend.
다들 재밌게 노세요
서브웨이에서 5달러 짜리
We got you half a dozen
five-dollar foot-longs
from Subway.
1피트 샌드위치 6개 사왔어요
That's six feet
o' meat.
그니까 6피트인 거예요
Five-- I ate a foot.
5피트야, 내가 하나 먹었어
넌 애가 진짜 왜 그러냐?
What is the
matter with you?
다들 고마워
Thanks, boys.
덕분에 맛있게 잘 먹을게
Gonna be quite a tasty event.
Thank you.
고마워
자 여기 먹어
Here we go, gentlemen.
내가 한 얘기가 이거예요
See, this is what
I'm talking about.
술에 잔뜩 취해서
카드 키를 훔쳐도
He's going to be so drunk
when you steal his card key,
he won't even
notice.
눈치 못챌 거예요
No tranqing
necessary.
진정제는 필요도 없죠
And how are we gonna
distract him?
어떻게 시선을 돌릴 건데?
Oh, I'm one step
ahead of you, my friend.
다 생각해둔 게 있어요
I had Jeff hire some
exotic female entertainment.
제프한테 댄서들 몇을
부르라고 했어요
적어도 샌드위치는 맛있잖아
At least the sandwiches
are fresh.
제프리, 잠깐만
Wait, Jeffrey.
쟤 네 동생 아니야?
Isn't that your sister?
She gave us a deal.
거래를 제안해왔어
여보세요?
Hello?
Hey, babe, it's me.
자기야, 나야
척이랑 애들이
총각 파티 한다고 날 납치해왔어
Chuck and the boys kidnapped me
for my bachelor party.
그래? 운 좋네
Wow, lucky you.
I am lucky, knowing
what's waiting
for me at home.
자기가 해줄 일을 생각하니까
나 정말 행운아다
Hey... great party, huh?
파티 재밌죠?
That's very charming for a man
who's so close to temptation.
유혹을 눈앞에 둔 사람치고
귀여운데
집에 스테이크가 있는데
햄버거에 눈이 가겠어?
How could I
be tempted
by a hamburger
진심이야, 사랑해
Seriously, babe, I love you.
알았어, 아부 그만해
All right,
you've sucked up enough.
난 자기 믿어, 재밌게 놀아
I trust you. Have fun.
고마워 자기야
Thanks, honey.
지갑을 빼왔는데 허탕이야
Got Woodcomb's wallet,
but came up empty.
카드 키가 없어
No card key.
목에 걸고 있나봐
Must still be around his neck.
We'll have to get it
another way.
다른 방법을 찾아야겠어
걱정마
Don't worry.
생각해둔 게 있어
Got a backup plan.
아직도 여기 있네
You're still
here, Walker.
I thought I made
myself clear.
알아듣게 말했다고 생각했는데
I'm just tying up
some loose ends.
마무리를 하는 것뿐이야
Make it quick.
빨리 해
모두 꼼짝마
Freeze, boys.
다들 혼쭐을 내주지
You're all in trouble.
경찰이다!
Five-O.
Got to flush my stash.
빨리 약 버려야겠다
아냐, 제프
네가 기다렸던 순간이 온 거야
No, no, Jeff, no, this
is what you've
been waiting for.
This... is Xanadu.
무릉도원 말이야
너희들 중 하나가
나쁜 짓을 했다던데
I understand one of you
has been a naughty,
- 누구지?
- 저요, 제발 저예요, 저
- naughty boy.
- Me... oh, my God, pick me.
I'm so bad, I've been bad,
I'm a bad person.
저 진짜 나쁜 짓 했어요
저 나쁜 놈이에요
I'm a terrible person-- ouch.
저 끔찍한 짓을 했어요
I broke eight
and a half commandments
on the way to work
저 오늘 아침에 출근하면서
십계명 8개 반이나 어겼어요
여기요, 이 사람이에요
This is your guy.
This is him.
I'm going to have
to strip-search you.
알몸 수색을 해야겠어
좀 도와줘
Uh, help.
싫어 / 됐어
No, no, no.
안 도와줄 거야?
A little help here?
No, no, you're under arrest.
안돼요, 체포된 거예요
I can't help you.
못 도와드려요
This is the law,
this is the law.
법이에요, 법
법을 어길 순 없으니까
못 도와드려요
We're not going
to go against the law.
Be gentle with him.
살살하세요
Oh, my.
세상에, 믿겨져?
Are you kidding me?
저기요, 쟤들이 이러라고
시킨 건 알겠는데
Listen, I know the guys
probably put you up to this,
but we really don't have
to be alone in here.
그렇다고 단둘이
이럴 필요까진 없잖아요
Oh, my...
맙소사
잠시만요
Wait... hey.
Why don't you just
take this off?
우선 이것부터
빼는 게 어때요?
That way, nothing's going
to come between us.
그럼 우릴 가로막는 건
아무것도 없을 것 같은데
안 돼요
I can't.
I lose it, I, uh... I get fired.
이거 잃어버리면 직장에서 잘려요
아뇨 아뇨 잠시만요
Uh, no, no, no, hold on.
Hold on, stop.
그만 하세요
Stop.
멈추세요
I love my fianc?.
전 제 약혼녀를 사랑해요
그 친구를 상처줄 일은
하고 싶지 않아요
I would never do anything
to jeopardize that.
버뱅크엔 아직
로맨스가 살아 있는 모양이네요
Guess romance is alive and well
and living in Burbank.
안돼요!
No, no, no!
진정제를 안된다고 했잖아요!
I said no tranqing!
That is not
no tranqing!
내가 안된다고 했죠!
Can't you keep
your stinking CIA darts
out of people?
수고했어
Good work.
Now I can access the
restricted area and plant
the bug before
이제 아마드 수술 전에
제한 구역에 가서
도청기를 심을 수 있겠어
다들 확실히 속은 것 같아
Be sure and sell it
for the friends.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
have I no rights?
내 생각은 전혀 안해요?
You can't just go around
willy-nilly
knocking out my family members.
막무가내로 내 가족을
기절시키면 안돼죠!
이미 한 것 같은데
Looks like we can.
새라라면 이러지 않았을 거예요
Sarah never would've done this. You've gone too far.
당신이 너무 지나쳤어요
Back off, Bartowski.
What are you gonna do about it?
- 그만해, 바토스키
- 그래서 뭘 어쩔 건데?
장군님한테 전화하겠어요
I'm calling the General,
that's what.
Is that so?
No one's calling anyone.
- 그러셔?
- 아무도 전화 안해
Listen, this 49-B stuff is over.
이제 49-B인가 뭔가는 끝이에요
From now on, the only person
I work with is Sarah.
지금부턴 새라하고만 일하겠어요
Walker's gone;
she's been dismissed.
새라는 떠났어
쫓겨났지
뭐라고요?
What?
What are you talking about?
그게 무슨 소리에요?
내가 네 새 담당자야
I'm your new handler.
우드콤 박사의 카드키를 써서
With the use of Dr. Woodcomb's
card key, Major Casey entered
the hospital's restricted area
케이시 소령이 제한 구역에 들어가
and planted the GLG-4000
on Ahmad's pacemaker.
아마드의 맥박 조정기에
GLG-4000을 심었네
장군님?
General Beckman?
잠시만, 바토스키
One moment, Mr. Bartowski.
Turn up the volume.
소리를 켜보게
That is the sound of success.
바로 성공의 소리지
General?
장군님?
Soon Ahmad and his men
will be on their way back
to Khalid's Afghani hideout,
아마드 일행이
아프가니스탄에 있는
카미드의 은신처로 돌아가는대로
and we can begin our covert
surveillance in earnest.
본격적으로 감시를 시작할 것이네
General, look,
I understand that this is
an important mission, I do.
장군님, 이게 정말 중요한
임무라는 거 저도 압니다, 알아요
하지만 새라는요?
But what about Sarah?
How can she be gone
just like that?
어떻게 그런 식으로
보낼 수가 있어요?
It's the way
it is, Bartowski.
원래 그런 거야, 바토스키
No, why didn't you tell me that
this could happen with a 49-B?!
왜 49-B 가 이런 일과
관련된 거라고 말씀 해주지 않으셨어요?
I was under the
impression that Agent Forrest was here
just to evaluate Sarah.
전 포레스트 요원이
새라를 평가하러 온 줄 알았는데
You lied to me!
거짓말 하셨군요
Come on, it's a job, Chuck.
그만해, 이 일이 원래 그래
No, for you, it's a job.
아뇨, 케이시한테야 일이겠죠
나한텐 내 인생이에요
For me, it's my life.
We disclosed everything
that was pertinent to you.
우린 자네와 관련된
모든 것을 알아야 하네
That's the way the National
Security Agency operates.
그게 우리 NSA가
일하는 방식이야
익숙해지도록 해
Get used to it.
가서 무기 청소나 해야지
I'm gonna go
clean my weapons.
When it comes to security,
보안에 대해서는
one can never be too cautious.
항상 조심, 또 조심해야해
Who is Rashad's doctor?!
라시드 의사가 누구지?
외과의 중 하나가
도청기를 심었어
One of the surgeons
put a bug inside him.
Dr. Devon Woodcomb.
데븐 우드콤 박사
You two go bring me the doctor.
자네 둘은 의사를 데려와
When the doctor
woke up this morning,
오늘 아침에 일어나서
he didn't know that today...
모르겠지
오늘이 바로..
나 죽었다
I'm gonna die.
세상에
Oh, my God,
I'm going to die.
I would love to
feel sorry for you, honey,
이제 죽었다
정말 유감이라고 해주고 싶지만
but I think you kind of
brought this one on yourself.
하지만 자기가 너무 많이 마셨어
How'd I get so wasted?
어떻게 이렇게까지 취했지?
하나도 기억이 안나
I don't remember a thing.
Well, you drank a little bit,
조금씩 마시다가
갑자기 마셔서 그래요
you cut loose,
no harm done.
그치만 아무 일 없었어
I remember
our lovely neighbor, John Casey,
친절한 이웃, 존 케이시가
술이랑 싸구려 스프레이 냄새
풀풀 풍기면서
carrying you home
at 4:00 in the morning,
smelling like booze
and cheap hairspray.
새벽 4시에 자길 데려왔어
Does that ring
a bell for you?
뭐 기억 나는 거 없어?
Honey, I mean, please
don't say the word bell.
자기야, 기억 얘긴 하지도 마
자기야?
Honey?
어제 나 카드키
안 갖고 들어왔어?
Did I have my key card
on me last night?
응?
What?
Did you take my key card
off me or not?
자기가 어제 내 카드키 뺐어?
No, I didn't take
your key card off.
아니, 그런 적 없는데
여기 어딘가 있겠죠
I'm sure it's here somewhere.
맙소사 안돼
Oh, God.
It's always around your neck,
under your shirt.
항상 목에 걸고
셔츠 안에 넣어 뒀었잖아
셔츠는 왜 벗었는데?
Whdid your shirt come off?
바지는 제대로 입고 있긴 한 거야?
Well, do you want to tell me
if your pants stayed on?!
엘리, 제발 카드키 찾는 것 좀 도와줘
Ellie, please, will you just
help me look for the key card?
Guys, guys, it'll turn up,
카드키는 곧 나타날 거예요
I just know it.
내 말 믿어요
You know, I'm, I'm really sorry
that you don't remember
what happened last night.
당신이 어젯밤 무슨 일이 있었는지
전혀 기억이 안난다니
정말 유감이야
I hope whatever it was,
it was worth it.
어제 뭘 했든간에
그럴 가치가 있었길 바래
어젯밤으로 다시 돌아가고 싶어
Dude, I wish I had a do-over
for last night.
다 되돌리고 싶다
I'd take it all back.
워커 믿어?
Can you believe Walker?
워커가 뭐?
What about her?
척하고 그런 사이인 거 말야
Getting all wrapped up
in the asset?
Clearly her feelings have
jeopardized your missions.
분명 임무 수행에 방해가 됐을 거 아냐
You must be relieved
that she's gone.
이제 떠났으니 맘 놓았겠네
이젠 프로답게 일할 수 있겠지
Things can now finally
be professional.
포레스트 요원
Agent Forrest,
for the record...
확실히 말해두겠는데..
우리 도청기에 문제가 생겼거나
Either something's wrong
with our equipment...
아마드한테 문제가 생긴 거야
Or something's wrong with Ahmad.
케이시 나에요
Hey, Casey, it's me.
캡틴 카드키 빨리 안 돌려주면
Look, uh, we got to get Awesome
his key card back
직장에서 곤란해질 거예요
or he's going to be
in big trouble.
빨리 그 의사 찾아야 돼
We must find this
doctor at once.
Which one is
his apartment?
어디가 그 의사 집이지?
안돼, 좋지 않아
정말 정말 좋지 않아
?????
안녕하세요 우드콤 박사입니다
Hi, I'm Dr. Woodcomb, can...?
정부 물품이야
Government issue.
Doesn't make any...
말이 안돼잖아
This...
이건..
맙소사
천국에 온 것 같은 냄새야
Oh, my God,
it smells like Heaven.
누가 슈가 쿠키를 구웠거나
아님...
Okay, that means either someone
is baking sugar cookies
or that is...
??????
모건 / 누나
I need to ask you a favor.
너한테 부탁이 있어서 왔어
Anything, anything--
you can have my firstborn.
뭐든지 말씀만 하세요
다 들어 드릴게요
어젯밤 총각 파티에서
무슨 일이 있었던건지 알려줘
I need to know
what happened last night
at Devon's bachelor party.
에이 누나
그런 걸 물으시면 어떡해요
Come on, El, you
can't ask me that.
남자들끼리 일이잖아요
There's a bro code.
부탁할게, 모건
Please, Morgan.
죄송해요, 말 못해요
I'm sorry, I can't.
말 안하기로 했어요
I have to lock it down.
저기 누나, 제 얘기 좀..
I just-- that's what I--
but listen to me, I...
세상에
Oh, my God.
그러게요
I know.
우리의 첫 총각 파티가
진짜 끝내줬..
Can you believe our
first bachelor party was
so freaking awes--?
누나
Ellie.
잠시만요
Wait,
wait, wait,
누나, 누나, 엘리 누나
Ellie, Ellie, Ellie,
엘리자베스, 엘레노어, 엘튼!
Elizabeth, Eleanor, Elton.
아무것도 없어
Got nothing.
나도
Me neither.
케이시
Casey.
I can't get in.
I don't have access.
들어갈 수가 없어
거부됐어
She's off the assignment.
이미 임무에서 제외된 요원이야
척이 위험에 처한 것 같아
Look,
I think Chuck's in trouble.
He never goes anywhere
without his phone.
핸드폰 두고는 아무데도 안가잖아
맞는 말이야
She's right.
포레스트, 아까 하려다가
못한 말인데
Now, Forrest, what I was
going to say earlier--
난 네 평가에 동의하지 않아
I disagree
with your assessment.
어느 부분이?
About what?
워커 얘기
Walker.
워커 요원은 프로야
She's a pro.
게다가 내가 같이 일했던
요원들 중에 최고야
Not only that, she's the best
damn partner I ever had.
척한테 작별 인사하러
갔다가 발견했어
I found this when I went
to say good-bye
to Chuck.
그렇담 내 명령에 불복종한 거야
Which directly
disobeyed an order.
그게 바로 애초에
네가 해고된 이유였지
You were fired
for exactly
this reason.
Then there's nothing stopping
me from kicking your ass.
그럼 내가 널 걷어차도
아무 상관 없겠네
척은 안마당에 있어
Chuck's in the courtyard.
잘 있다고
He's fine.
아마드 심장에서 오던
신호가 끊겼어
We lost the surveillance
signal from Ahmad's heart.
분명 척이 사라진 것과도
관련이 있을 거야
Got to be a
connection
between the signal's
그게 무슨 소리야
I don't understand.
GLG-4000은
아프가니스탄 동굴 안 속에서도
Isn't the GLG4000
specifically designed
to track deep inside
작동할 수 있게
특별히 제작한 거 아냐? / 맞아
You'd need at least six feet
of solid steel
to block that signal.
신호가 차단되려면
적어도 강철 6피트 두께는 필요해
여기가 신호가 사라지기 전
신호가 온 마지막 장소야
This is the last location
his heart registered
before going off-grid.
위성 사진하고 같이 띄워봐
Overlay the satellite image.
잠시만
Wait a minute.
은행 금고 안에 있는 거야 / 그래
They're in a
bank vault.
Yeah,
- 그럼 신호가 없어질 만하지
- 수고했어, 워커
that would do it.
Great work, Walker.
좋아요 우드콤 선생
Okay, Dr. Woodcomb,
time for you
to remove the bug
당신이 내 친구 안에 심은
도청기를 제거 해줘야겠어요
내 친구를 살리지 못하면
And if you don't
save him,
당신도 죽게 될 겁니다
nothing can save you.
이제 환자는 잠들었어요
The patient
is now fully under.
좋아요, 좋아
잘하셨어요
Cool.
Cool, good, good.
수고하셨어요
Well done there.
바로 그렇게 하는 거죠
That's how we do things.
제가 집중할 수 있게
I'm going to need
to take a minute
just so that I
잠시만 기다려 주세요
괜찮으시면 침착한 상태에서
수술하고 싶군요
if you will.
I, uh,
need a mellow headspace
when I operate.
Quit stalling, Dr. Woodcomb.
시간은 그만 끄시죠
I'm a little out of
practice, honestly.
사실 제가 하도 오랜만이라..
Maybe if you could do it.
Cut him open...
- 선생님이 해주시면..
- 어서 절개하세요
아님 당신을 절개 시켜줄테니까
or I'll cut you open.
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
I'm bleeding!
어떡해! 어떡해!
저 피나요
Oh, my God,
I'm bleeding.
Come on.
- 세상에, 나 피나
- 나 원 참
I'm sorry, I just get a little
woozy at the sight of blood.
죄송해요 제가 피를 보면
어지러워지거든요
외과의가 피를 무서워한다?
A surgeon who is afraid
of blood?
I know-- a little ironic, right?
알아요, 아이러니 하죠?
Get the door,
get the door!
문을 닫아! 어서!
Get the door!
문 닫아!
chuck
Who the hell is Chuck?
Huh? Chuck... Chuck?
- 척이 누구지?
- 네? 척이요?
No clue... I have no clue.
글쎄요, 전 전혀 모르겠는데요
I'm Dr...
I am Dr. Woodcomb, okay?
전 우드콤 박사예요
아님 데븐이나 박사님도 괜찮고
Oh, yeah?
Or Devon or Doc.
가끔 캡틴짱이라고 불리기도 해요
Or sometimes people
call me Captain Awesome,
그치만 척은 누군지 전혀 모르겠..
but I have no idea who this...
who this Chuck...
아, 이 척 말씀이시구나
Oh, you mean that Chuck.
You're a dead man, Chuck.
넌 이제 죽었어, 척
척이 인터폴 수배자랑 같이
안에 갇혀있잖아
Now Chuck is
locked inside
with one of Interpol's
It is your job
to protect him, damn it.
척을 보호하는 게
네 일이잖아, 젠장
I've got nitroglycerin
and a blasting cap
in the van.
밴 안에 니트로글리세린과
뇌관이 있어
I'll have this door off
in no time.
곧 문을 뜯어낼 수 있을 거야
Hold on, I think I saw
a nitrous setup in there.
잠깐, 금고 안에서
질소 장비를 본 거 같아
You're gonna blast
the door open,
문을 폭파시켰다간
are you're gonna kill Chuck
in the process.
척이 죽게 될 거야
이리 와!
Come on, come on!
What makes you think
he's not already dead?
벌써 죽었을지도 모르잖아?
Come here!
이리 안와!
뭐에요?
What?
왜 웃어요?
What... what is it?
I forgot why I was mad at you.
내가 왜 너한테 화났는지 까먹었어
I was gonna cut you with this.
이걸로 너 자르려고 했었는데
이상해
That's odd.
I think I hear Chuck laughing.
척 웃음 소리가 들려
Here, give me
the walkie.
무전기 줘 봐
I'll handle it.
내가 알아서 하지
You're lying.
거짓말이지
No, I'm not.
아냐, 진짜야
Think about it.
생각해봐
무당벌레(Ladybug)라고
다 여자(Lady)일리가 없어
Ladybugs can't
all be ladies.
I mean, that's
just crazy.
그게 말이 되냐고
그럼 아기 무당벌레가
어떻게 있겠어?
Then, how would we get
little ladybugs?
무슨 소린지 알지?
You know
what I mean?
Chuck, can you hear me?
척, 내 말 들려?
Hey, your
pocket's talking.
네 주머니에서 목소리가 나
Oh, hey, can
I get that?
내가 받아도 돼?
Yeah.
그럼
Hi.
안녕, 안녕
네, 잘 들려요
Hi, yeah, I'm fine.
잘 있어요
I'm fine.
I'm... I'm also
high from nitrous,
그리고 나 지금 질소에 취했어요
but so is... so is my
man, Zamir, here, so...
여기 내 친구, 자미르도요
But I'm not coming out
until you find Sarah
and you bring
근데 당신들이 새라 찾아서
여기 데려오기 전엔
절대 안 나갈 거예요 / 그래
That's right.
Stand your ground.
네 의사를 확실히 해
하산 칼리드처럼
Like Hassan Khalid.
Hey, where is
that guy, anyway?
근데 그 사람은 지금 어딨어?
'Cause I haven't seen
him around in a while.
한동안 통 안보이던데
카라코람 산맥
동쪽의 동굴에 있어
(파키스탄 카시미르 북부 산맥)
He's in the Eastern
Karakoram caves.
All right.
그렇구나
Good for him.
잘 됐네
He's a bad dude, huh?
정말 나쁜 사람이야 그치?
Hey, Chuck,
turn off the gas, idiot.
질소 가스 꺼, 이 멍청아
You inhale too much
of that stuff, it'll kill you.
너무 많이 들이마시면
죽을 수도 있어
우리 죽는대
We're going to die.
You're gonna die!
너 죽는대!
당장 문 열어
Open this door
right now.
싫어
No, look,
I'm not listening to you, okay?
내가 왜 당신 말을 들어야 하는데?
This isn't working.
이런 식으론 안돼
I can't risk this
going any further.
더 이상 위험을
감수할 순 없어
I'm getting the nitro.
니트로글리세린 가져올게
Forrest, we can
do this your way,
포레스트, 네 방식대로
할 수도 있지만
or we can
actually save
the asset.
내 방식으로 척을 살릴 수도 있지
???Here.
Sarah.
척 / 새라
정말 당신이에요
Is it really you,
or am I
super stoned?
아님 내가 그 정도로
취한 거예요?
Uh, both.
둘 다요
Both Rashad Ahmad
and Dr. Zamir are in custody.
라쉬드 아마드와
자미르 박사 모두 수감 중이네
Though the mission didn't go
according to plan,
임무가 계획대로
진행되진 않았지만
척이 하산 칼리드의 은신처를
알아내준 덕이네
Chuck was able to ascertain the
hidden location of terrorist,
Hassan Khalid.
수고 많았네
포레스트 요원
Thank you, Agent Forrest.
Just doing my
job, General.
제 일을 했을 뿐입니다
워커 요원
Agent Walker,
despite your heroism,
자네의 용기있는 행동에도 불구하고
you have directly disobeyed
several orders.
자넨 여러 번 명령에 불복종했네
잠시만요 장군님
Wait, General.
I'm sorry, but-but...
isn't the most
죄송하지만 제 담당자로서
가장 중요한 역할은 제 안전을
important part
of being my handler making sure
that I stay
- 지켜주는 것 아닐까요?
- 척, 괜찮아요
It's okay, Chuck.
아니, 아니야
No, it's not.
마저 얘기해
Let him finish.
고마워요
Thanks.
네, 장군님
Um... General...
제가 드리고 싶은 말씀은..
what I'm trying
to say is that...
I think that maybe because my
relationship with Sarah is so...
어쩌면 저와 새라와의 관계가..
가깝기 때문에..
You know, we're...
we're close.
저흰 서로를 아껴요
We care about
each other.
That's what I'm
trying to say,
제가 하고 싶은 말이
그거에요
and I know it's not
protocol or whatever,
절차에 어긋난다는 거 알지만
but it's those feelings
that wound up saving my life.
바로 그 때문에 제가
계속 살아 남아 있을 수 있는 겁니다
포레스트 요원은
Agent Forrest diagnosed
your emotional connection
as a liability.
자네 둘의 감정 때문에
임무에 지장이 있다고 평가했네
But I suppose
it can also be an asset
to the...
하지만 그게
장점이 될 수도 있겠군
척에게 말이야
well, asset.
복직하도록 하게, 워커 요원
You may resume your post,
Agent Walker.
We hope not to see you too soon,
Agent Forrest.
한동안 만날 일이 없었으면 좋겠군
포레스트 요원
That's all.
이상이네
no, this isn't...
this isn't what you think.
누나, 누나가 생각하는
그런 거 아냐
아니긴 뭐가 아니야, 척
Yes, it is, Chuck.
It's exactly what I think it is.
내가 생각하는 바로 그건데
I can't believe that you
are covering for him.
네가 데븐을 감싸주다니
믿을 수가 없다
총각 파티에서 아무 일도 없었어
Nothing happened
at the bachelor party.
He didn't do anything,
I swear it.
데븐, 아무 짓도 안했어
정말이야
Chuck, I saw the photos, okay?
척, 나 사진 다 봤어
알겠어?
미안해
I'm sorry.
I know you're just trying
to protect him.
데븐을 보호하려고
그런단 거 알아
Bro code, whatever,
남자들만의 일이라 이거지
but, Chuck, Iam your sister.
하지만 척, 난 네 누나야
You're supposed to protect me.
그럼 날 보호해줘야 하는 거잖아
Sarah, please,
I am freaking out, okay?
새라, 나 정말 미치겠어요
I don't know
who else to talk to,
더 이상 곤란하게
하고 싶지도 않지만
but I also don't want to get you
in more trouble at work.
새라 말고
말할 사람이 없어서 왔어요
It's okay-- this is
my private residence.
괜찮아요
여긴 내 집이니까
There is no surveillance
that can talk to me.
도청같은 건 없어요
말해봐요
I don't know
what to do.
어떻게 해야 할지 모르겠어요
Ever since you guys
rolled into town,
새라랑 케이시가
나타난 이후 부터
my life has been... has been
spinning out of control.
내 인생은 통제 불능이 되버렸어요
My whole world
is about juggling lies.
온통 속임수에
거짓으로 가득해졌어요
꼭...
It's like...it's like this.
이거 같아요
I bet this is a...
what, a submachine gun?
이거 기관단총 같은 거죠?
No, it dries
my hair.
아뇨, 헤어 드라이기에요
알았어요, 어쨌든
모든 게 망가졌어요
Okay, fine, but everything else
is completely screwed up.
I just want to be able
to tell Ellie the truth
about who I am and what I do.
누나한테만큼은
솔직하게 말해주고 싶어요
내가 누구고
뭐하는 사람인지요
정부가 내가 사랑하는 사람들에게
엄청난 상처를 주고 있어요
I can't believe how much
the United States Government
has hurt the people that I love.
이젠 정부가 척을
도와줄 때가 된 것 같네요
Well, maybe it's time
for the United States Government
to help you.
Chuck, you saved my life, man.
척, 네 덕에 살았어
카드키 찾아줘서 고마워
Thanks for finding my key card.
척?
Dude?
Special Agent Carmichael.
카마이클 특수 요원님
Well, you, uh...
새라, 아마도..
법 여러 개는 어겼겠네요?
probably had to break
a few rules, huh?
Go on, knock.
가서 두드려봐요
I couldn't find him.
찾을 수가 없었어요
The man didn't want
to be found.
누가 찾길 바라지 않았던 거예요
I mean...
내 말은..
법도 어기고 정부 주요
데이터베이스까지 검색해야 했잖아요
you had to illegally
access the government's
master database to...
Chuck.
척
It will be good to see him.
그래도 만나뵙는 게 좋겠어요
유감이에요
아빠?